YUNTING SHAO

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Artistic Video editor with outstanding proficiency in Adobe Premiere Pro and Adobe Photoshop and multi-camera editing expertise in video productions and also creative design. Efficient and reliable with passion for bringing creative projects to duration. Reliable intern studying post production seeks an internship opportunity to expand skills and gain valuable real - world experience to seek and maintain a position that offers professional challenges utilizing interpersonal skills, reliable with time management and problem - solving skills. Reliable team member with strong communication skills and ability to adjust work for various environments. Handles modifications, requests and feedback from colleagues, clients and vendors in efficient manner, understanding needs of all parties involved. Flexible in adapting work style to fit different projects and juggling multiple assignments within tight deadlines. Artistic Designer experienced with wide variety of design tools and comfortable working in both 2D and 3D environments. Strong understanding of user experience design and creating visually appealing and highly functional designs. Enthusiastic team player ready to contribute to company success.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts, Media Art And Performance - Creative Technologies, 06/2023

University of Regina - Regina, SK

Raymond and Helen McDonald Prize, 2023 From Campion College at the PROFILES University of Regina

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Food Safe, Saskatchewan Health Authority January 12, 2022
- Circular Economy For The Waste Sector In South Africa, United
 Nations Institute for Training and Research October 23, 2022
- An Introduction to Climate Change And Human Rights, United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change - October 23, 2022

- Regina, SK S4W 0T2
- 3065154650
- shaobilly@gmail.com
- Personal Website

WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/yunti ng-shao-2a5827207/
- https://www.artstation.com/svakbr is
- https://catssister.github.io/Spooke y-Ball-Robot

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office (Words, Excel and PowerPoint) Mac & Windows
- Logical recruiting with critical, analytical and creative thinking ideologies
- Creative Suite: Photoshop,
 Premiere Pro, InDesign, illustration,
 Bridge, Lightroom, DaVinci Pro,
 Final Cut Pro, Affinity Series,
 Ableton Lite,C4D, Blender, Maya,
 SolidEdge
- Photography Taking by severe composition and framing consideration
- Photoshop Raw filter advanced user
- 3D modeling, post production & installation
- Interior Desin
- Voice production: recording, capturing, editing
- Creative Visualization & aesthetics
- Design and print modeling 3D printer user

- Storytelling For Impact In Your Classroom: Photography, National Geographic - August 18, 2023
- Applying Geographic Thinking Skills with Your Learners, National Geographic - August 18, 2023
- The International Observe the Moon Night 2023 PARTICIPATION,
 NASA National Aeronautics and Space Administration August 21,
 2023
- National Geographic Photography, European Open University September 4,2024
- Body Language, Academy Europe open University September 4,
 2024
- Pain Management: The Role of Pain Psychology, Stanford University School of Medicine - September 10, 2024
- Autism and Neurodiversity in Early Childcare, The University of British Columba - September 11, 2024
- Rapid Teacher Training Programme on Distance, Open and Online Learning, United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization – September 11, 2024
- Masterclass On Artificial Intelligence, International Training Center –
 September 11, 2024
- Interior Desin, The Digital Adda September 11,2024

LANGUAGES

Chinese (Mandarin)

English

Native or Bilingual

Professional Working

WORK EXPERIENCE

Automotive Detailer, 07/2023 - Current

Enterprise Truck Rental, Regina, SK

- Vacuumed interiors of vehicles to remove dirt and debris.
- Maintained car detailing equipment and supplies in optimal condition for daily demands.
- Inspected interior and exterior of vehicles for cleanliness and accurately identified imperfections outside vehicle standards.
- Washed, waxed, and buffed vehicle bodies for professional shine.
- Maintained clean, tidy and safe work environment.

Ramp Service Agent, 02/2023 - Current

Alliance Ground International, Regina, SK

- Performance improvement
- Data Building and Modeling

- Eagerness to learn new Technologies
- Mandarin native speaker and fourteen years English speaker
- Strong interpersonal and Communication skills
- Food preparation and safety
- Active Listening
- Fashion Design
- Creative Design Layouts
- Early Child Care
- Online Teaching program

- Analytical Thinking and Problem Solving
- Strong Interpersonal and Communication Skills
- Eagerness to Learn New Technologies
- Message Translation between Chinese and English
- Ethical Codes Adherence
- Microsoft Office, Communicated closely with ground crew, flight crew, and tow person via headset radio to maintain loading and unloading safety and efficiency
- Safely operated various types of equipment such as conveyor belts, push-back tractors and tugs
- Performed mathematical functions to interpret aircraft weight and balance loading instructions
- Loaded and unloaded luggage and freight and assisted crew and travelers with bags for over 10 daily flights
- Coordinated ground crew activities to complete objectives on schedule
- Cleaned airplanes between flights, sanitized lavatories and seat trays as per company specifications
- Operated equipment while observing standard safety procedures
- Verified quantity and description of materials received by checking merchandise against packing list
- Verified documentation and condition of freight to assure quality standards were achieved.

CSL Tax Professional, 02/2023 - 05/2023

H&R Block, Regina, SK

- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity
- Carried out day-day-day duties accurately and efficiently
- Demonstrated respect, friendliness and willingness to help wherever needed
- Worked flexible hours; night, weekend, and holiday shifts
- Performed duties in accordance with applicable standards, policies and regulatory guidelines to promote safe working environment
- Maintained energy and enthusiasm in fast-paced environment
- Offered friendly and efficient service to customers, handled challenging situations with ease
- Served customers and followed outlined steps of service.

Radio Frequency Identification, 07/2022 - 11/2022

Regina Public Library, Regina, SK

- Quickly learn database organizing skills to speed up work efficiency
- Accurately and efficiently complete the record of daily book electronic ID
- Flexible working hours, weekend and night shift

- Be energetic and enthusiastic in a fast and efficient working environment
- Use critical thinking to solve problems in different ways
- Keep good attendance records and arrive at work on time
- It reflects a good technical level and has a good understanding of digital book management system
- Maintained energy and enthusiasm in fast-paced environment
- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions and make decisions
- Actively listened to customers, handled concerns quickly and escalated major issues to supervisor.

Teaching Assistant, 01/2022 - 04/2022

University Of Regina, Regina, SK

- Support in-depth research on topics of the week
- Use visual aids and remote technical support to help professors teach
- Assist professors in the management and coordination of students' homework to ensure a positive learning environment
- Assisting the professor to enter the students' homework and exam scores through the online system
- Presented wide range of information to students using hands-on instructional techniques for effective comprehension
- Supported planning and preparation for culturally-diverse class sessions
- Worked with teachers to optimize learning plans based on student test grades and evaluations.

Distribution Clerk, 05/2018 - 08/2021

Great Asian Market, Regina, SK

- Documented stock records and schedules accurately
- Scheduled pickups and deliveries to maintain smooth operations
- Accelerated consumer purchasing habits by increasing distribution and availability across range of retail outlets
- Uncovered and resolved errors with minimal oversight
- Collaborated with other departments on supply and quality issues
- Managed and maintained warehouse to comply with company policies and federal regulations.

Food Deliverer, 04/2017 - 01/2021

Skip The Dishes, Regina, SK

- Completed on-time deliveries by choosing the best and most efficient routes
- Verified daily deliveries against shipping instructions before delivering to customers

- Kept detailed records of completed or in-progress deliveries using hand-held devices and camera images
- Created and submitted delivery and DOT logs
- Communicated regularly with the dispatcher for delivery route details and changes
- Processed payments, made changes and provided receipts
- Immediately addressed problems with customers to promote speedy resolution